vrs-design.myshopify.com 2017-03-15

# Privacy & Terms | VRS Design®

### Privacy & Terms

This website ("VRS DESIGN") is operated by VRS Design Inc. This privacy policy only covers information collected at this website, and does not cover any information collected offline by VRS Design Inc. 

All VRS Design Inc. websites are currently covered by this privacy policy.

#### Our Commitment to Privacy

At VRS DESIGN, we value our customers’ right to privacy.   
VRS Design’s Privacy Policy is to help our customers understand how we collect, secure, and use the information our customers provide to us at vrsdesign.com.   
We recommend that our customers review our Privacy Policy if they are concerned about how the information is used.

### Terms

#### Online Account Registration

When you register on vrsdesign.com, you make your shopping experience faster and easier. If you have registered an account with us, your billing address, shipping address, and account information only need to be entered once and will be securely stored in our database. You will be able to access your account online to modify or delete information. For non-registered users, we request for email, billing, and shipping information for each purchase.

#### Information Collected by vrsdesign.com

When you shop at vrsdesign.com, we collect information we need to complete your transaction. Information we collect may include your Name, Shipping Address, Billing Address, Telephone Number, Email Address.

We value your privacy. Your personal information will never be shared to third parties.

#### Billing Information

We use this information to confirm your payment information such as credit/debit card information. We may use this information to contact you regarding your order.

#### Shipping Information

We use this information for activities such as shipping your order.

#### Email Information

We use this information to send you updates about the orders that you place or send you company and product updates through newsletters you subscribe to. 

#### Cookies

Cookies are small data texts files that web browsers save when you visit some websites. We use cookies to make your shopping experience on vrsdesign.com more convenient and more personalized. For example, you can retrieve an earlier saved shopping cart with the saved cookies on your web browser.
